If you really say you're married,
prove it!
Kiss each other right now.
If that's all you need.
A kiss? A kiss?!
That's… um…
That's right!
I've heard that your first kiss
tastes like lemon!
That would go well with this
marinated dish!
Relax, Yor. Keep it together!
Well then…
W-W-W-Wait a minute!
I can't do it if I'm sober.
Thanks for waiting.
Huh? O-Okay.
If you don't want to, we don't have to.
No, this is for me too. I'll do my best.
What are you two mumbling about?!
Can you do it or can you not?!
Prove that you're a real married couple!
Shut up, Yuri.
We're going to show off
how much we're in love.
Here I go, darling. Close your eyes.
S-Sis!
Huh? Yor?
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION:9 SHOW OFF HOW IN LOVE YOU ARE
Sis!
How lewd!
Look! I got the best test score
in my class!
Wow! That's great!
Here's a congratulatory kiss!
Sis…
When I get older,
I'm going to marry you.
Oh!
Then I'll have to wait for you!
…Wait for you…
wait for you…
No, Sis!
I don't want you to
kiss another man in front of me!
Absolutely not!
I knew it… No!
No!
It's the end of the world!
Huh? Yuri?
Fine, Sis…
The fact that you rejected my attempt
to stop you two from kissing,
must mean that you really wanted to
make out with that guy.
It was foolish of me to test you.
It seems like
my feelings were being tested instead!
Um, maybe we should stop that bleeding…
Loid Forger…
I'll put you in charge
of my sister's lips for now!
What are you saying?!
I'll give it a rest for today… But…!
Um… The bleeding…
Is this normal in the Briar family?
Are you okay, Yuri? You're wobbling…
-It's all because of you…
-I'm fine…
You're wobbling too…
Shall I call you a taxi?
I'm fine. You worry too much.
Why are you smirking?
You find my humiliation so amusing?
Oh, no.
I was just thinking
what nice siblings you are.
I can tell
you've always supported each other.
Yuri,
thank you
for protecting Yor all this time.
I'm sure you've been through
some tough times.
I'll do my best to support her
from now on too,
so let's work together to make Yor happy.
Who would ever need your help?!
Forget it! I'm leaving!
Please come again anytime!
It'll make Yor happy and next time,
please come when our daughter is awake!
Anya was trying so hard
to wait up for you!
She's very cute,
so please play with her next time.
I'll come even without you telling me!
Next time I'll find proof that
you're tricking my sister!
I'm not being tricked!
Listen, Loid Forger.
If you do anything to make Sis cry,
I'll make sure to exe…
Um… It's… Basically…
Anyway, I'll make you regret it!
Be careful! If you yell,
you'll bother the neighbors!
Was he about to say "execute"?
I'll have to be careful.
There aren't any
bugs hidden here.
As Secret Police, or rather,
as her brother, I wouldn't be surprised
if he did. I have to be careful.
-Thank you, Loid.
-Hm?
I'm ashamed to say this,
but thank you for accepting
such a rude kid as your family.
Yuri really loves you.
I don't have any friends or family that
I can depend on, other than my daughter,
so I was actually a bit envious
of the two of you.
Loid…
Although she's my fake daughter…
At any rate, I'm relieved that
we weren't exposed as a fake couple.
Yes!
Now that I'm relieved, I'm tired.
Let's go to bed after we clean up.
Of course, I'll return it back
to the way it was before!
Yes!
Father!
Save the world…
Yuri, I'm going to get mad
if you hit Loid…
I don't remember the last time
I was envious of someone.
I'm going to sleep.
It's probably just because I'm tired.
The mission will continue tomorrow.
Excuse me!
Which way is the station?
-Go to the hospital first!
Morning…
Father, you're a bit green today…
Stop dreaming and go wash your face.
Good morning!
I'm sorry you couldn't meet
Yuri yesterday.
Who is that?
What? But she was so excited!
It was quite lively yesterday, huh?
I'm sorry…
I couldn't believe
Yor's brother was like that.
Oh! Uncle!
And to top it off, he's Secret Police.
Such a nuisance to a spy.
Secret Police?!
What is that?
Secret and police?
How exciting!
Why didn't you introduce Anya?!
Give me back my excitement!
You wanted to meet him that badly?
Well, we survived one storm…
I need to focus on Anya's studies.
Come on, hurry and eat.
You're going to be late.
You'll meet him soon.
Are we really free from any concerns?
Yor Briar, who has a brother
in the Secret Police.
There was nothing suspicious about her.
Nor did she seem to know
who her brother was.
My gut feeling is that she's in the clear.
She wouldn't have worried about
people suspecting her singleness
if she'd known that he was
Secret Service personnel.
No, it's dangerous to be definite.
What if it was all an act and a lie,
to get close to me from the beginning?
Question everything, Twilight.
Father, Mother is…
What is it?
Mother…
sucks at cooking.
She figured out
that I made breakfast today!
I'm sorry! I tried my best…
-Oh, Yor?
-Yes?
Um…
Will I be going too far
if I plant a bug on her?
No, I have to be cautious.
A moment of negligence leads to death.
It's a matter of life and death
for tens of thousands of people.
To be certain of Yor's innocence, I must…
You have some lint on your collar.
Oh! Thank you.
He scared me!
I thought he was going to kiss me goodbye!
What?!
The aftermath of yesterday
is still lingering…
I can't cook, and I can't kiss…
Loid did a good job
of smoothing things out yesterday, but…
I'm probably doing an awful job
of acting as a wife.
Somehow,
I feel that Loid's
a bit distant from me today.
Perhaps he's upset with me
for my inadequacy.
I have to be vigilant.
What's wrong, Anya?
Father and Mother need to get along.
We're not fighting or anything.
That's right!
You need to get along with
your classmates too!
-Then, shall we?
-Yes.
Children are so sensitive sometimes.
Hey Yuri,
how did you get those injuries?
I thought you went to congratulate
your sister on her marriage.
I don't really remember…
You probably got drunk
and picked a fight with her husband.
Stop drinking already.
I can't give my sister up to him.
Was he that bad?
I think he was…
a good guy…
But con artists and spies
act like good guys all the time!
Yes, he must be a spy!
Then we can put him in jail!
Relax. Do you have any proof?
Darn it!
I forgot to plant a bug
in the living room and bedroom!
Oh, no! I can't do that!
I won't be able to handle it
if I hear her voice
while she's doing this and that!
Did you cause those injuries?
Get off your sister's back already,
so you can focus on work.
We have a mission to capture
the spies of the West,
especially Twilight.
In turn, that will help keep
your sister safe.
I know. But as for now…
Loid Forger…
On the day that you make Sis cry, I'll…
What's wrong with her?
She was saying something about
how she's an unfit wife.
-Hey.
-Oh, Sharon!
Huh? How to be a good wife?
Are you two not getting along?
It's not that… it's just that…
I've never dated someone before,
so I don't really know how to act.
Based on my past relationships,
I wondered if
Yor had never been with a man before.
I guess I was right.
I don't know how to explain it,
but I don't think it's okay the way it is.
I can't even cook!
Anya's words must've hurt her.
Is Yor trying to become a better wife
so we can
better disguise ourselves as a family?
No, wait.
It's possible that she's trying to
play the perfect wife
in order to deceive me.
It's disastrous when there's too much of
a spectral difference between a couple.
Why don't you break up with him?
I can't do that…
The relationship between
Yor and her colleagues is a bit…
Hey!
Stop chatting and work!
Ugh! Manager…
Hey, Yor.
I'm sorry but can I ask you to
take this to the post office?
Of course.
The only way to get any kind of
decisive result
is to initiate it from my side.
Come to think of it,
Loid and I have different accounts.
If I combine some of
my earnings from my work,
would I be able to help Loid as a wife?
But I can't have him be suspicious…
And I feel like it's not about
helping him financially…
Hey lady. We need to ask you something.
May we have a moment?
The Secret Police!
Have I done something?
Was it suspicious that I was looking at
a pamphlet meant for couples, even though
I don't seem like I'm married?!
I'm married!
We're not hitting on you.
What is this?
You call me out of the blue, only to have
me wear this and investigate your wife?
Just do it as we planned.
It's for the mission.
That has nothing to do with me!
We're the ones who weigh the mail.
The sealed letter you just sent out,
is probably a coded document
addressed to the West.
The sender, Barnes, is your boss?
-Yes.
-What's your name?
Yor Br-- Yor Forger.
Oh. So you're Yor Forger?
Your name is written right here.
Maybe you're an accomplice?
You're so into it…
So you were working together?
I don't know what you're talking about!
It has to be a mistake!
It's in your best interests to be honest.
A man in the finance department at
City Hall was caught just the other day,
and it appears that internal corruption
has advanced considerably.
I hear that the end of him was tragic.
I heard that he was
tortured so severely that
he even lost his mind
and committed suicide in prison!
Last month, a woman about her age
was also dragged away!
You know, the congressman's secretary?
What type of character is he playing?
The guy had a Security Service agent
in his family, so he was released.
That's one of our privileges!
The family of a bureau member can
get away with most charges!
Well, anyway, we'll have you
come to the detention center with us.
If you know that your brother is
a Security Service officer, you can just
mention Yuri's name and it'll all go away.
There's no reason to keep secrets
between colleagues,
and if she makes a big fuss,
it'd raise suspicion
among his colleagues and me.
Come on, Yor.
If you're in the black,
ask your brother for help!
Otherwise…
I work day to day
for the people of this country.
I would never be a spy!
There's no point acting innocent!
Just be good and come--
Ouch!
I told you I was married.
Don't put your hands on me so easily.
Don't think that you and your family can
get away with this kind of behavior.
My brother and husband are both
very kind and good citizens.
If you intend to harm them unjustly,
I will not tolerate it,
even if I have to take you on!
Hey, Lieutenant Mop?
Is this cipher really correct?
Huh? It can't be… Oh! This is--
Upon closer look,
it's not the raccoon code!
It's the caterpillar code!
Upon re-deciphering, this appears to be
a letter from Mr. Barnes to
an avowed hemorrhoid doctor.
Huh?
I see. He was too embarrassed
so he encrypted it.
How troublesome.
So it seems that the espionage charge
was a mistake.
Your name's not on here either.
You can go home but don't mention this to
anyone in order to keep Mr. Barnes' honor.
That was a complete farce.
Well, I think it's safe to believe that
she has no connections
with the Secret Police.
What is it?
Don't tell me you feel guilty
for doubting her.
That's not it.
I warned you before,
don't let your emotions get involved.
If you want to keep living,
don't trust anyone.
That's the only way
people like us survive.
You saying that with that face
pisses me off.
You're the one who made that face!
Damn! I thought I'd get
some ladies with that face!
My handsome face!
I don't think it's good to date a woman
based on lies.
You have no right to say that.
Today was so nerve-racking.
I almost got arrested…
Not only am I an awful wife,
I almost broke up the Forger family!
-Oh, Yor!
-Loid!
What a coincidence.
Shall we go home together?
Hm? You have some lint
on your collar again.
I'm sorry
that I'm a wife who can't even
keep my appearance together.
You know what I think, Yor?
I think most families in this world
are living their life
while acting out a role.
Like "a wife should be this,"
or "Because I'm a parent…"
Of course, it is wonderful to
work on being the ideal figure.
However, nothing will work out
if you lose sight of yourself
by binding yourself to those ideals.
Many people suffering from that
come into our hospital.
You'll get tired
if you're constantly playing a role.
Loid…
So, please, be yourself.
If you're confident, no one will know.
I'm sure Anya will be happier
if you're smiling.
Thank you. I…
I'm glad that you're the person I married!
Don't tell me you feel guilty
for doubting her.
What did you just throw away?
The lint I took off earlier. By the way,
we didn't do anything
for our one-year marriage anniversary.
-Shall we buy some cake on the way home?
-Yes!
Father! Mother! Anya is back!
Welcome home, Anya!
What's wrong?
Father and Mother are getting along!
I told you we weren't fighting!
We have cake, Anya!
I want to eat cake!
Hey, you're making too much noise
for our neighbors downstairs!
MISSION:10 THE GREAT DODGEBALL PLAN
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi